{
    "id": "cf52657204c545cfb2f9c41ea6e94c3d",
    "title": "Gap Fills Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "He died two months ………………………",
            "description": "We use ago to count back from a present moment.",
            "answers": [
                "before",
                "ago",
                "back"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "She was clever ……………………………….. to solve the puzzle.",
            "description": "Enough shows sufficiency. It goes after the adjective or adverb it modifies.",
            "answers": [
                "enough",
                "too",
                "so"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I wish you …………………………….. behave like this.",
            "description": "Would is used after wish to talk about people’s insistence.",
            "answers": [
                "wouldn't",
                "won't",
                "hadn't"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "You ………………………….. be in trouble if she fails to recognize you.",
            "description": "In the first conditional, we use a simple present tense in the if-clause and will + infinitive in the main clause.",
            "answers": [
                "will",
                "would",
                "would have"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "We ought to invest in health and education …………………………….. infrastructure.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "than",
                "would rather",
                "rather than"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "I would rather be a writer ………………………… a doctor.",
            "description": "We use than after rather.",
            "answers": [
                "to",
                "than"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Tired ………………………….. she was she went shopping.",
            "description": "As and though can be used after an adjective or adverb. In this case, they both mean although.",
            "answers": [
                "though",
                "as",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………………………… she was tired, she went shopping.",
            "description": "We use though to connect two contrasting ideas. ",
            "answers": [
                "As",
                "Though",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Such was her beauty ………………………. men from far and near came to woo her.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "as",
                "that",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Strange ……………………….. it may seem, I don’t like music of any kind.",
            "description": "As and though can be used after an adjective or adverb. In this case, they both mean although.",
            "answers": [
                "as",
                "though",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "If you marry me, I will give you ……………………….. freedom as you want.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "as",
                "as much",
                "more"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "She is as …………………………. nails.",
            "description": "We use a positive adjective in the expression ‘as…as’.",
            "answers": [
                "hard as",
                "harder as",
                "harder than"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        }
    ]
}